http://www.inserso.com/info/privacy

Home
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
This notice discloses the privacy practices for Inserso.com and the information collected by this website.
The primary purpose of the Inserso website is to be a tool to help you learn more about our company. We want you to feel secure when visiting our website and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so.
What information do we gather?
We may collect and process the following information:
Our website collects information about your computer, including your IP address to report on statistics.
We analyze your IP and browser information to help us identify ways to improve it and make it more effective.
Our website collects details of your visits to our website, the pages you view and resources you access or download. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any individual user.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
Links to Other Websites and Services
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Questions on Privacy
If you can't find what you're looking for here, or have a concern about our use of your personal data, please Contact Us.
Last updated October 5, 2017
